globegain.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy

**What personal information do we require?**

We require your personal information when you register on our website, add a rebate account or place a withdrawal order. This information may include your name, email address, phone number, credit card or bank account details or the details of your account in another payment system. However, you may visit our website anonymously.

**What do we use your personal information for?**

Any of the information required by us may be further used for the following purposes:

\- _To personalize your experience_ (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- _To improve our service_ (we continually strive to improve our service based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- _To improve customer service_ (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

\- _To process transactions._ Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the requested service.

\- _To send periodic emails._ The email address you provide to register on our website and to have your requests processed will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to the above-mentioned issues.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please email [support@globegain.com](mailto:support@globegain.com) with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line.

**How do we protect your personal information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our service policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personal visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to the information collected through our website and not to the information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
